<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Lost Saga In-Depth Blog</title>
        <link>https://trisnox.github.io/en/blog</link>
        <description>Lost Saga In-Depth Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Read Mercenary Information]]></title>
            <link>https://trisnox.github.io/en/blog/how-to-read-mercenary</link>
            <guid>https://trisnox.github.io/en/blog/how-to-read-mercenary</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Use image as referece.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Use image as referece.</p><p><img loading="lazy" alt="Mercenary Summary" src="/en/assets/images/table1-4244f76dc02407044cc6c5be7c7f0fab.png" width="1300" height="336" class="img_ev3q"></p><ul><li><code>ID</code> mercenary code. Every mercenary have unique code attached to them</li><li><code>Name</code> mercenary name</li><li><code>Sprint</code> indicates if this mercenary can run</li><li><code>Jump</code> maximum jump this mercenary could do</li><li><code>Attack Length</code> attack length from <code>Ground</code> attacks</li><li><code>Highest Damage</code> the most damaging attack this mercenary had</li><li><code>360 Block</code> indicates if blocking will also protect hits from back</li><li><code>Deflect</code> indicates if mercenary block will deflect enemy (must block at perfect time to deflect)</li><li><code>Counter</code> indicates if mercenary able to perform a counter attack when attack button is pressed when blocking a hit</li><li><code>Down Hit</code> list of attack that are able to hit downed enemy</li><li><code>Special</code> gauge/bullet usage on mercenary</li><li><code>Unique Property</code> unique property this mercenary had</li><li><code>Dump</code> additional info</li></ul><p><img loading="lazy" alt="Mercenary Attacks" src="/en/assets/images/table2-00c568a04ed0a7d9696dd6bc105a0c08.png" width="684" height="908" class="img_ev3q"></p><ol><li>Attacks name</li></ol><ul><li><code>Ground</code> attacks when being done while idling/walking</li><li><code>Dash</code> attacks when being done while running</li><li><code>Dash Replace</code> this mercenary cannot run, if attempting to run, this attack will be used instead</li><li><code>Jump</code> attacks when being done while at air</li><li><code>... Jump Hold</code> attacks when you hold attack button much longer</li><li><code>Charged</code> attacks when you hold attack button much longer during idling/walking</li><li><code>... Extend</code> follow-up attack when you press attack button</li><li><code>... Hold</code> attacks when you hold attack button much longer</li><li><code>Counter</code> attack when you press attack button while blocking a hit from enemy</li></ul><ol start="2"><li>Attacks attribute</li></ol><ul><li><code>Damage</code> damage caused by that attack</li><li><code>Defense Break</code> indicates if this attack break enemy's block</li><li><code>Juggle</code> how high the enemy will be lifted when hit with this attack during some state (eg: faint)</li><li><code>Air Juggle</code> if the enemy is on air, this indicate how much enemy will be lifted with this attack</li><li><code>Down Hit</code> indicates if this attack can hit downed enemy</li><li><code>Push Power</code> indicates how strong this move to push enemy (on ground)</li><li><code>Frozen Break</code> indicates if this attack would break enemy frozen state</li></ul><ol start="3"><li>If this column exist, this means that this attack is a multi-hit (hits more than once)</li></ol>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Author's Note]]></title>
            <link>https://trisnox.github.io/en/blog/init-release</link>
            <guid>https://trisnox.github.io/en/blog/init-release</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Initial release note. This wiki is made for educational purposes. Usually, Lost Saga in-game/website doesn't contain enough information about hero/gear. That's why I made this wiki to gather all the data on heroes and gear data so that we could know more about its mechanics, property, and attributes.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Initial release note. This wiki is made for educational purposes. Usually, Lost Saga in-game/website doesn't contain enough information about hero/gear. That's why I made this wiki to gather all the data on heroes and gear data so that we could know more about its mechanics, property, and attributes.</p><p>Currently, I'm working alone. If you wish to contribute/suggest/fix (typo, incorrect information, missing information), you can contact me via <code>discord: trisnox</code>, submit <a href="https://github.com/Trisnox/lost-saga-in-depth-info/pulls" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">pull request</a>, or submit <a href="https://github.com/Trisnox/lost-saga-in-depth-info/issues" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">issue</a>. For discord, you can contact me through DMs or from a discord server directly, I urge you to not bring this subject on LSO Valofe discord server, thanks.</p><hr><p>Small lore, everything starts where I had thought of extracting models from Lost Saga, that I later <a href="https://youtu.be/DLYl9QIcmUM" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">turn it into animation</a>.  After some though, almost all resource are available on that archive, this includes: hero data, gear, shop, PvP/PvE mode, and many more.</p><p>This file contains detailed information about said item, I was surprised by just looking at it knowing that no one knew about such information.</p><p>For instance: scientist helm lvl 3 doesn't give you damage bonus buff, but rather cause your attack to inflict a poison debuff when landing a hit on enemy. This poison lasts for .1s and every .05s enemy loses health for 2%.</p><p>Not even developer/GM would give such information, hence why I create this wiki to provide information to all Lost Saga player.</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>